wonderfuldiy.com 2018-10-22

# Privacy Policy - WonderfulDIY

Your pri­vacy is impor­tant to us. We wrote this pol­icy to help you under­stand what infor­ma­tion we col­lect, how we use it, and the choices you have regard­ing your infor­ma­tion. Please take a moment to famil­iar­ize your­self with our pri­vacy policy and email us if you have any questions.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which [www.wonderfuldiy.com](http://www.wonderfuldiy.com/) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.wonderfuldiy.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by [www.wonderfuldiy.com](http://www.wonderfuldiy.com/).

**Infor­ma­tion We Col­lect** **** We may col­lect non-personal infor­ma­tion about Users whenever they interact with our Site, such as the browser type, lan­guage pref­er­ence, refer­ring site, and the date and time of each vis­i­tor request. Our pur­pose in col­lect­ing this non-personal infor­ma­tion is to bet­ter under­stand how Users use our Site.

**Web Browser Cook­ies** **** Cookies are tiny text files that a web­site stores on a visitor’s com­puter and that the visitor’s web browser pro­vides to the web­site each time the vis­i­tor returns. We use cook­ies to help us iden­tify Users, their usage of our Site, and their web­site access pref­er­ences. You can dis­able cook­ies in the pref­er­ence panel of your web browser (check with your provider to find out how to dis­able cook­ies). Please note that cer­tain fea­tures of the website may not be avail­able once cook­ies are disabled.

**How we use collected information** www.wonderfuldiy.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve customer service_ Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _To improve our Site_ We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _To send periodic emails_ We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

**Sharing your personal information** We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites** Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our Site. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the users based on their visit to our Site and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**Your Acceptance of These Terms** By using our Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Pri­vacy Ques­tions** If you have any ques­tions or con­cerns about this Pri­vacy Pol­icy, please email us at: wonderfuldiysite@gmail.com.

**Changes in Pri­vacy Pol­icy** **** We may update this Pri­vacy Pol­icy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the updated Pri­vacy Pol­icy on our web­site. We advise review­ing this Pri­vacy Pol­icy periodically for any changes.

All materials, unless otherwise noted, were taken from the Internet and are assumed to be in the public domain. All the pictures and videos shown on icreativeideas.com are the property of their respective owners. All sources we use to create our articles are and will be credited with a proper link back. However, we are hosting a lot of uncredited material from unknown authors we received via mails, from friends and our readers. If you own copyrights to some material such as images and you want us to remove it from our pages, contact us to claim your ownership and we will either credit you and your website, or if you wish – completely remove the content. Please be assured that the break of the copyright is unintentional and noncommercial and the materials will be removed immediately upon presented proof. Contact: [wonderfuldiysite@gmail.com](mailto:wonderfuldiysite@gmail.com)

wonderfuldiy.com cannot accept any responsibility for any injury or damage that you may cause to yourself, others, or property when following any advice given on this site. wonderfuldiy.com has no control of how you may use information you get from this site and does not attest to the validity of any information found within. Much of this information comes from third parties. Please use advice found on our site at your own risk.
